Jonathan Moore

MIDI Association Expert, Audio and Software Engineer and Scholar

jdm7dv@gmail.com

Summary

I began my professional career right out of high school in technical support and development as a Macromedia User Group then later worked for Adobe and FreeBSD volunteer and contributor. At the same time pursuing my associates and bachelors in computer science. I was also a web developer for the UVa-Wise Magazine. And member of the ACM. My complete discography is available on Bandcamp. I'm a BMI writer and publisher. I have been streamed worldwide with Tunecore And developed some small VST's and Rack Extensions for Propellerhead and Steinberg which never shipped. I recently became a Microsoft Visual Studio industry partner and created a Microsoft Research and Innovation group on Gitlab. Also trying to find some time for sound design and amateur asteroid hunting with MPC. I'm in the Virginia and National Associations for the Gifted since 2011 and Mensa groups here on LinkedIn And IEEE Computer Society also a member of the Mensa High IQ society on LinkedIn I also have been a Microsoft MVP. I am wanting to pursue gifted studies at the University of Connecticut maybe. I scored a 140 on the Mensa mobile app. And sometimes I vent on my own personal profile on social media, but never in the communities. Sixtrack is the infrastructure that helps upgrade the LHC.

Experience

Summer Internship at Hewlett Packard Enterprise

June 2017 - Present

Working on "The Machine"

Rack Extension Engineer at Propellerhead Software

February 2016 - Present

Rack Extension and VST developer.

Ambient Musician at DBA

March 2005 - Present

Visual Studio Industry Partner at Microsoft

October 2007 - Present

Currently at individual status. And a linked Microsoft Research Github. And owner of the Microsoft Research Group on Gitlab. Former Office 365 Partner.

Software Engineer Contributor at FreeBSD

March 2001 - October 2016 (15 years 8 months)

I build the FreeBSD OS, kernels and help with bugs.

Technical Support at Macromedia

December 2000 - October 2006 (5 years 11 months)

Audio Engineer

April 2002 - December 2004 (2 years 9 months)

Used VST plugins

Education

University of Virginia

Bachelor of Science, Computer Software Engineering, 2008 - 2013

Activities and Societies: ACM

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

Open Courseware, Various OpenCourseware, 2016

Stanford University

Stanford Online, Quantum Mechanics for Scientists and Engineers, 2016

Tennessee Technological University

Associate's Degree, Computer Science, 1998 - 2001

Jonathan Moore

MIDI Association Expert, Audio and Software Engineer and Scholar

jdm7dv@gmail.com



Contact Jonathan on LinkedIn